Um, does Pottery Barn,
Spring count?
(Beverly:)Penny, it's only natural to want
your mother-in-law to like you,
(Beverly:)and I acknowledge I can be
an intimidating person.
(Beverly:)So what can I do to make
this process easier for you?
(Penny:)Uh, for starters,
(Penny:)maybe you can not psychoanalyze
everything I say?
(Beverly:)And how does it
make you feel
(Beverly:)when I psychoanalyze
everything you say?
(Penny:)Uncomfortable.
(Beverly:)That was a joke, dear.
(Penny:)Oh. Sorry.
(chuckles)
Didn't know you made those.
(Penny:)Hey, listen, what
if we have a little
mother-in-law-daughter-in-law
dinner tonight?
(Beverly:)So just the two of us?
(Penny:)Or I invite a few girlfriends,
(Penny:)'cause hearing you say
“the two of us”
(Penny:)just sent a chill
right down my spine.
(car door opens)
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Amy:)What are you doing here?
(Amy:)You're not Sheldon.
(Stuart:)I thought that might come up.